Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to Reel Tapes, 1961-1984
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1961-1984, I.; Item 1-123
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 052, 1976-10-17, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1976 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.2 (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Leo Smit, piano, speaker; Winifred Simpson, soprano; Heinz Rehfuss, bass-baritone; and Robert Moran, stage direction
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_052_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_052_01-08pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_052_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_052_01-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 053, 1976-10-31, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1976 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.3 (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet; Joseph Kubera, piano; Keiko Yamazaki, violin; Stephen Marvin, viola; Lynn Wullen, violin; Bonnie Black, cello; and Albert Furness, chimes Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 1 of 2 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Diabolus in musica...: The experimental decade inserted; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 53 and 54 07: Histoire - 1 file per each of the 1st 6 works Derivative files created: 7 (Box 4, Item 53)
    ips
    Contents: Prokofiev: Overture on Hebrew themes -- Fantome -- Toccata; Webern: Vier Stücke, op. 7; Schoenberg: Sechs kleine Stücke, op. 19; Berg: Vier Stücke, op. 7; Stravinsky: Histoire du soldat; Cowell: The banshee; Scriabin: Sonata no. 9, "The black mass"; Hauer: Labyrinthine dance; Ives: Three-page sonata -- Halloween
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_053_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_053_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_053_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_053_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_053_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_053_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_053_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_053_01-07pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_053_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_053_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_053_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_053_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_053_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_053_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_053_01-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 054, 1976-10-31, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1976 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.3 (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet; Joseph Kubera, piano; Keiko Yamazaki, violin; Stephen Marvin, viola; Lynn Wullen, violin; Bonnie Black, cello; and Albert Furness, chimes Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 2 of 2 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Diabolus in musica...: The experimental decade inserted in Tape 53; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 53 and 54 01: Prokofiev -- 07: Histoire - same content as Tape 53. Derivative files created: 7 (Box 4, Item 54)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_054_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_054_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_054_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_054_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_054_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_054_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_054_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_054_01-07pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_054_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_054_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_054_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_054_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_054_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_054_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_054_01-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 055, 1976-10-31, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1976 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.3c (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet; Joseph Kubera, piano; Keiko Yamazaki, violin; Stephen Marvin, viola; Lynn Wullen, violin; Bonnie Black, cello; and Albert Furness, chimes Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 1 of 2 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Diabolus in musica...: The experimental decade inserted; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 55 and 56; check contents in case this was labeled incorrectly as concert 3 in the series 01: Mikhashoff intro and Histoire 2nd part - 02: Intermission recording Mephisto Waltz, Berlin Karajan - Cowell not performed - 03: Intermission and Yvar's explanation of why the Cowell is not being performed - 04: Scriabin - 05: Hauer - 06: 3-page - 07: Halloween Derivative files created: 7 (Box 4, Item 55)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_055_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_055_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_055_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_055_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_055_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_055_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_055_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_055_01-07pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_055_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_055_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_055_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_055_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_055_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_055_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_055_01-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 056, 1976-10-31, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1976 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.3c (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Allen Sigel, clarinet; Joseph Kubera, piano; Keiko Yamazaki, violin; Stephen Marvin, viola; Lynn Wullen, violin; Bonnie Black, cello; and Albert Furness, chimes Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 2 of 2 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Diabolus in musica...: The experimental decade inserted in Tape 55; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 55 and 56; check contents in case this was labeled incorrectly as concert 3 in the series Same as 55 Derivative files created: 7 (Box 4, Item 56)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_056_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_056_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_056_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_056_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_056_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_056_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_056_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_056_01-07pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_056_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_056_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_056_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_056_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_056_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_056_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_056_01-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 057, 1976-03-14, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1976 The Masque of the Winter's Tale Performers: Cambiata Soloists, Mikhashoff, piano, director; Isabelle Ganz, mezzo-soprano; Diane Tobola, soprano; Patti Spain, mezzo-soprano; Stephen Bates, recorders; Tim Brace, Wolfgang Justen, guitar; Richard Brown, percussion; Wayne Crouse, viola; Richard Nunemaker, clarinet; Paul Schmidt, speaker; Mary Schoettle, piano; Amy Winn, flute Recording location: Houston, University of St. Thomas, Jones Hall Photocopy of printed program inserted; Première performance; ballad opera in three parts; scenario by Paul Schmidt, after Shakespeare. One of four works originally on the program 1 work, 1 file Derivative files created: 1 (Box 4, Item 57)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: The masque of the winter's tale
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_057_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_057_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_057_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 058, 1977-05-15, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1977 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.10 (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 1 of 3 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Signoff... Inserted; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 58, 59, and 60 5 files matching 1st 5 works Derivative files created: 5 (Box 4, Item 58)
    Contents: Copland: Piano blues; Smit: Sonata. Finale; Satie: Choses vues à droite et à gauche; Feldman: Durations 2; Cowell: Hymn and fuguing tune no.9; Hiller: Sonata no.2. Larghetto and finale; Bartók: Sonata. Chaconne and fugue; Mikhashoff: Prelude, variations and fugue; Cage: Tossed as it is untroubled -- Music for Marcel Duchamp -- Prelude for meditation -- 4'33''
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_058_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_058_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_058_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_058_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_058_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_058_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_058_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_058_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_058_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_058_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_058_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 059, 1977-05-15, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1977 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.10 (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; and Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 2 of 3 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Signoff... inserted in Tape 58; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 58, 59, and 60 01: Hiller - 02: Bartok Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 59)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_059_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_059_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_059_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_059_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_059_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 060, 1977-05-15, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1977 The Contemporary Piano Concert No.10 (3) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; and Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 3 of 3 Photocopy of printed program for concert titled Signoff... inserted in Tape 58; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 58, 59, and 60 Mikhashoff - Cage works Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 60)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_060_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_060_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_060_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_060_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_060_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_060_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_060_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_060_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_060_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 061, 1977-02-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. piano #6 / #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 1 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled The great american quest, concert no. 6 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 61, 62, and 63 Harris, Johnson, Thomson: spoken intro only Derivative files created: 3 (Box 5, Item 61)
    Contents: Harris: Prelude; Johnson, Hunter: Piano sonata; Thomson: Pastorale: Portrait of Jeanne Ozenne – Portrait of Aaron Copland; Copland: Piano variations; Sellars: Sonata for piano; Barber: Sonata for piano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_061_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_061_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_061_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_061_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_061_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_061_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_061_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 062, 1977-02-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. piano #6 / #2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 2 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 61 for concert titled The great american quest, concert no. 6 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 61, 62, and 63 01-02: Thomson portraits - 03" Copland - 04: Sellars Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 62)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_062_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_062_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_062_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_062_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_062_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_062_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_062_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_062_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_062_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 063, 1977-02-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. piano #6 / #3 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 3 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 61 for concert titled The great american quest, concert no. 6 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 61, 62, and 63 1 file, 1 work Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 63)
    Contents: Barber: Sonata for piano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_063_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_063_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_063_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 064, 1977-04-17, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. piano concert 8 / #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, harpsichord, piano; Isabelle Ganz, mezzo-soprano; Heinz Rehfuss, bass-baritone; Baird Contemporary Ensemble; University Winds; James Kasprowicz, Carlo Pinto, conductors Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 1 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled After the fall...: Music in Germany 1918-1938, concert no. 8 in the series, The contemporary Piano; handwritten note "Interview Cuts" on front of container; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 64, 65, and 66 Includes spoken introductions. 2 files 2 works Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 64)
    Contents: Hindemith: Song for St. Martin's day; Webern: Variations op.27
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_064_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_064_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_064_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_064_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_064_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 065, 1977-04-17, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. piano concert 8 / #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, harpsichord, piano; Isabelle Ganz, mezzo-soprano; Heinz Rehfuss, bass-baritone; Baird Contemporary Ensemble; University Winds; James Kasprowicz, Carlo Pinto, conductors Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 2 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 64 for concert titled After the fall...: Music in Germany 1918-1938, concert no. 8 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 64, 65, and 66 Includes spoken introduction. List of performers incorrect. They are announced on file 3. 3 files, 3 works Derivative files created: 3 (Box 5, Item 65)
    Contents: Traditional, arranged by Silcher: Aennchen von Thurau; Schoenberg: Thema mit Variationen; Eissler: Cantata in exile
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_065_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_065_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_065_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_065_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_065_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_065_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_065_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 066, 1977-04-17, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. piano concert 8 / #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, harpsichord, piano; Isabelle Ganz, mezzo-soprano; Heinz Rehfuss, bass-baritone; Baird Contemporary Ensemble; University Winds; James Kasprowicz, Carlo Pinto, conductors Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 3 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 64 for concert titled After the fall...: Music in Germany 1918-1938, concert no. 8 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 64, 65, and 66 Includes spoken introductions. Berg is missing. This is the Weill Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 66)
    Contents: Berg: Thema scherzoso con variazioni; Weill: Threepenny opera suite
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_066_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_066_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_066_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 067, 1977-05-12, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. #9 (1) Performers: Baird Contemporary Ensemble, Mikhashoff, piano; Carol Plantamura, soprano; John Boudler, percussion; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Jan Williams, conductor; Nora Post, oboe; James Kasprowicz, conductor; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 1 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted for concert titled The new abstraction, concert no. 9 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 67, 68, and 69 Includes spoken introduction. 2 files, 2 works. 2nd file includes spoken intro to Messiaen work on Tape 67. Performers for Messiaen stated. Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 67)
    Contents: Stockhausen: Kreuzspiel; Berio: Sequenza III
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_067_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_067_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_067_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_067_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_067_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 068, 1977-05-12, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Cont. #9 (2) Performers: Baird Contemporary Ensemble, Mikhashoff, piano; Carol Plantamura, soprano; John Boudler, percussion; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Jan Williams, conductor; Nora Post, oboe; James Kasprowicz, conductor; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 2 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 67 for concert titled The new abstraction, concert no. 9 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 67, 68, and 69 2 files, 2 works. Both files begin abruptly. Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 68)
    Contents: Messiaen: Colors of the celestial city; Foss: Time cycle
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_068_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_068_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_068_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_068_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_068_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 069, 1977-05-12, 1 5 inch reel; Container title: [Cont. #9 (3)] Performers: Baird Contemporary Ensemble, Mikhashoff, piano; Carol Plantamura, soprano; John Boudler, percussion; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Jan Williams, conductor; Nora Post, oboe; James Kasprowicz, conductor; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: University at Buffalo, Katherine Cornell Theatre Reel 3 of 3 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 67 for concert titled The new abstraction, concert no. 9 in the series, The contemporary Piano; Entire contents listed but it is not clear how the contents are divided between Tape 67, 68, and 69 Check: 1 file Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 69)
    Contents: Stockhausen: Kreuzspiel; Berio: Sequenza III; Messiaen: Colors of the celestial city; Foss: Time cycle
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_069_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_069_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_069_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 070, 1978-11-30, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Bussotti Operaballet Performers: Mikhashoff, piano, speaker; William Kirkpatrick, dancer-choreographer Recording location: Baird Hall, University at Buffalo Photocopy of printed program inserted 8 works, 8 files Derivative files created: 8 (Box 5, Item 70)
    Contents: Bussotti: Foglio d'album -- Ankibathes -- Musica per amici -- Sensitivo -- Parfum -- Novelletta -- Per tre -- Foglio d'album
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_070_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_070_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_070_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_070_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_070_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 071, 1978-09-06, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: John Cage Apartment house 1776 Tape no. 1 for performance Performers: James Kasprowicz, trombone; Mikhashoff, piano; Stephen Bradley, electronics Recording location: Baird Recital Hall, University at Buffalo Reel 1 of 2 Photocopy of printed program inserted; the complete program included Hindemith: Sonata for trombone and piano; DeLeeuw: Music for trombone; Carr: The bells of San Blas; Wolff: Exercises 15-18 but based on the container's marking it appears like only the Cage is on the tape. The contents are also divided between Tape 71 and 72. There is a spine label that is apparently incorrect: 1975 The great keyboard sonata (Jackson) 4 files Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 71)
    15 ips
    Contents: Cage: Solo for sliding trombone and Piano concert with Apartment house 1776
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_071_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_071_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_071_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_071_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_071_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_071_01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 072, 1978-09-06, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: John Cage Apartment house 1776 (#2) performance tape Performers: James Kasprowicz, trombone; Mikhashoff, piano; Stephen Bradley, electronics Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Reel 2 of 2 Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 71; the complete program included Hindemith: Sonata for trombone and piano; DeLeeuw: Music for trombone; Carr: The bells of San Blas; Wolff: Exercises 15-18 but based on the container's marking it looks like only the Cage is on the tape. The contents are also divided between Tape 71 and 72. There is a spine label that is apparently incorrect: 1973 Concerto by Colin McPhee (Johannesen); Note inside container: "And a Merry Christmas to you both, Christian." Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 72)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_072_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_072_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_072_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_072_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_072_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_072_02-01sc.mp3